<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NotesApplication</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="note_name">Note name</string>
    <string name="note_date">Note date</string>
    <string name="note_body">Note body</string>
    <string name="background_color">Background color</string>
    <string name="edit_note">Edit Current Note</string>
    <string name="palette">Palette</string>
    <string name="delete_note">Delete current Note</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="search_action">Search</string>
    <string name="cozy_view">Change view</string>
    <string name="save_note">Save</string>
    <string name="unsuccess_save">Save is not success!</string>
    <string name="success_save">Note saved</string>
    <string name="notes_drawer_action">Notes</string>
    <string name="notification_drawer_action">Notification</string>
    <string name="archive_drawer_action">Archive</string>
    <string name="basket_drawer_action">Basket</string>
    <string name="settings_drawer_action">Settings</string>
    <string name="help_feedback">Help/feedback</string>
    <string name="keep">Keep</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_one">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="toast_notification">Notification should here</string>
    <string name="display_options">Display options</string>
    <string name="add_new_notes_to_end">Add new notes to end</string>
    <string name="move_marked_items_to_the_end">Move marked items to the end</string>
    <string name="add_new_note">Add new note</string>
    <string name="success_add">Note add</string>
    <string name="user_avatar">User Avatar</string>
    <string name="delete_confirmation">Current Note %s deleted!</string>
    <string name="Undo">Undo</string>
    <string name="atention">Attention</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure">Are you really would like delete the Note?</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>


    <string name="title1">Anemona</string>
    <string name="description1">The genus of anemone has approximately 150 species of herbaceous plants growing in moderate zones of the Northern Hemisphere. Its tuberous and ...</string>
    <string name="title2">Anturium</string>
    <string name="description2">The beautifully flowering evergreen anthurium is more known as “Flamingo Flower” or “Male Happiness”. It belongs to the largest genus of plants from ...</string>
    <string name="title3">Arabis</string>
    <string name="description3">The genus combines more than 100 species growing from the Arctic to the tropical zone of Europe and South America. Perennial or ...</string>
    <string name="title4">Araukaria - coniferous plant ...</string>
    <string name="description4">Araukaria is a tree with unusual leaves. It can be grown in a pot - and this is one of the few coniferous ...</string>
    <string name="title5">Thrift</string>
    <string name="description5">About 50 species are known, wildly growing in Western and Eastern Europe, Siberia, Mongolia and America. Description of Armeria perennial herbaceous ...</string>
    <string name="title6">Astilba</string>
    <string name="description6">The name of Astilba comes from the Greek words a - very, stilbe - shine. It is probably given for brilliant leaves. Description...</string>
    <string name="title7">Astilboides</string>
    <string name="description7">The birthplace of Astilboides is China, where it grows through forest edges, ravines. Astilboides plate - perennial, 30 cm high ...</string>
    <string name="title8">Astra is many years old</string>
    <string name="description8">Description, types and varieties of Astra perennial asters belong to the Astrov family, that is, they are the closest relatives of the famous ...</string>
    <string name="title9">Astra is one -year -old</string>
    <string name="description9">We wrote about the long -term Astra in another article about Astra. Then we will analyze the one -year -old Astra. The genus of one -year -old astra has 1 ...</string>
    <string name="title10">Astra</string>
    <string name="description10">There are 10 types of aperture, in the natural conditions of growing in the Caucasus, in Asia Minor and Southern Europe ...</string>
    <string name="title11">Aukuba</string>
    <string name="description11">Aukuba belongs to the Kizilov family. Her homeland is Japan. Acuba Japanese is common in culture. Aukuba is an eternally green shrub, in ...</string>
    <string name="title12">Acidanter</string>
    <string name="description12">The genus has about 40 species found in the tropics of Africa. Acidanter is a cormation of a perennial plant resembling gladioli. Stems ...</string>
    <string name="title13">Badan</string>
    <string name="description13">Badan is a popular perennial plant, in one place it grows without a transplant for more than 10 years. Badan has a fat ...</string>
    <string name="title14">BAKOP</string>
    <string name="description14">A plant from the noricovik family. Originally from South Africa. In the culture of Bakop, she appeared since 1993. She was called ...</string>
    <string name="title15">Balsam</string>
    <string name="description15">Balzamine is a herbaceous plant of the Balsamin family. The Latin name Impatiens is not withstanding pressure. It reflects the property ...</string>
    <string name="title16">Barvinok</string>
    <string name="description16">Barvinok, or its other name of Winka (Vinca) is a well -eating or steady ground cover, kuts family. Barvinok grows very quickly ...</string>
    <string name="title17">Marigold</string>
    <string name="description17">The genus comes from America, where in the wild they grow from New Mexico to Argentina. More than 30 ...</string>
    <string name="title18">Begonia</string>
    <string name="description18">Begonia is from the tropics. Representatives of the Begonia family surprise us with their diversity of sizes, colors and shapes. Adult flowers ...</string>
    <string name="title19">Clulture begonia</string>
    <string name="description19">Recently, tuber begonia is common in gardening and landscaping. The reason for popularity was the successful work of breeders from different countries: ...</string>
    <string name="title20">Emergency</string>
    <string name="description20">Unreleal or its other name Colchikum - from the family of monodol plants, bended. Also known under the popular name ...</string>
    <string name="title21">Butterbur</string>
    <string name="description21">In the spring, along the edges of the edges or on the sidelines of arable land, it can be lucky enough to see wonderful dense white or pink spherical ...</string>
    <string name="title22">Beloperone - growing in ...</string>
    <string name="description22">Beloperone is one of the most decorative indoor plants that can be grown both indoors and on ...</string>
    <string name="title23">White flower</string>
    <string name="description23">The homeland is the Mediterranean, Central Turkey, Europe, Iran. The genus has approximately 10 species of bulbous plants, blooming early ...</string>
    <string name="title24">Bocarnea</string>
    <string name="description24">BEAUCARNEA is a perennial and evergreen plant, which belongs to the Nolinov family. It is divided into several types, each of ...</string>
    <string name="title25">Boltony</string>
    <string name="description25">In natural conditions, the genus has about 9 different species common in East Asia and North America. This...</string>
    <string name="title26">Brahcoma</string>
    <string name="description26">Brahcoma is an elegant annual (sometimes perennial), a strongly branched plant. The foliage of brachikoma is openwork, small, narrow, linear, green. On the bush ...</string>
    <string name="title27">Bravlia: landing and care ...</string>
    <string name="description27">Description of the plant Family: Annial - Solanaceae. Rod: Burtia - Browallia. Type: Brailia is beautiful (or magnificent) - Browallia Specios Hook. Broilia —...</string>
    <string name="title28">Brunner</string>
    <string name="description28">Brunner is a wonderful perennial. Beautiful Brunners of frosty-silver coloring will be the decoration of your flower garden. Brunner flowers of course, Brunner blooms (flowers ...</string>
    <string name="title29">Bugenville</string>
    <string name="description29">Bugenville - a flower is very unusual, starting from the name and ending with the appearance, in Germany many even call it ...</string>
    <string name="title30">Buznik</string>
    <string name="description30">Recently, Russian amateur gardeners began to show great interest in herbaceous decorative plants, which are distinguished by impressive dimensions. Among...</string>
    <string name="title31">Bouquet of roses - flower ...</string>
    <string name="description31">It always gives me pleasure to come on a date to a charming luxurious girl with a beautiful bouquet of wonderful flowers, fragrant ...</string>
    <string name="title32">Bouquet of flowers</string>
    <string name="description32">Every year, at the same time, in early spring, many men just take flower shops in ...</string>
    <string name="title33">Wallota</string>
    <string name="description33">Wallota is such a flower that it is very similar to the brothers from her family. You can distinguish it, for example, by characteristic ...</string>
    <string name="title34">Wanda</string>
    <string name="description34">Wanda orchids (lat. Vanda) - perhaps the most beautiful flowers from the orchid family. With good care, these elegant flowers can ...</string>
    <string name="title35">cornflower</string>
    <string name="description35">A cornflower flower is a plant for summer flower beds. Cold -resistant annual. Color - white, yellow, pink, red, blue, blue, purple. Flowering time ...</string>
    <string name="title36">Vasiliznik</string>
    <string name="description36">Vasiliznik (Talktrum) Description of the Vasilitnik Latin name: Thalictrum. Type: perennial. Height: 150-200 cm. Place: Shadow and partial shade. Soil: fertile, neutral, rich in humus. Propagation: Light. Care: Light. Basic...</string>
    <string name="title37">Cotton wool</string>
    <string name="description37">About 80 species of a cotton wool, which is common in South and North America. Grassy plants with horizontal, exit far ...</string>
    <string name="title38">Three -leaf shift - landing ...</string>
    <string name="description38">Watch, or rather, a three -leaf, very decorative swamp plant. It can successfully decorate ponds and ponds. In our...</string>
    <string name="title39">Loosestrife</string>
    <string name="description39">The verbaner belongs to the primary family. History of the name of the Verbeinik: It is believed that one of the types of verbanics described dioscoride and named ...</string>
    <string name="title40">Verbena</string>
    <string name="description40">The description of Verbena is as many among flowers such that they give us beauty, remaining little -known. Such is Verben. She was known again ...</string>
    <string name="title41">Verbena ampel</string>
    <string name="description41">Ampel is grown as an annual plant. A grassy flower is most often planted in suspended baskets, because the stems of verbena ...</string>
    <string name="title42">Veronica</string>
    <string name="description42">The genus includes 300 types of Veronica, common throughout the world, very widely in Europe. In Russia, 150 species, large ...</string>
    <string name="title43">Vertical gardening</string>
    <string name="description43">Vertical landscaping, in fact, is a garden: these are trees and shrubs planted on the site. They may not perform ...</string>
    <string name="title44">Vitaliana</string>
    <string name="description44">Vitaliana Primulocvetkova, or Dugnesia Vital (Vitaliana Primuliflora = Douglasia Vitaliana) is an elegant groundcover alpine plant of this. Primary ...</string>
    <string name="title45">Volzhanka</string>
    <string name="description45">Volzhanka or its other name Aruncus is a large, spectacular perennial plant. In appearance, the Volzhanka is very remembered by Astilba. The advantage of the Volzhanka ...</string>
    <string name="title46">Voronets</string>
    <string name="description46">In Russia, 3 types of Voronets are growing in total, they are all forest perennials, similar to each other. Types and ...</string>
    <string name="title47">Vrijesia</string>
    <string name="description47">Vrijesia is an unusually spectacular, beautiful home flower. This plant refers to the Bromeliev family and includes in its kind ...</string>
    <string name="title48">Growing pelargonium from seeds</string>
    <string name="description48">Most of us think that pelargonium is only a indoor plant, but, nevertheless, pelargonium grows perfectly and ...</string>
    <string name="title49">Growing petunia from seeds</string>
    <string name="description49">Probably everyone is interested in when to sow petunia for seedlings. As a rule, petunia seeds begin to sow in March. BUT...</string>
    <string name="title50">Growing a primrose from seeds</string>
    <string name="description50">Growing a primrose from seeds is not a simple occupation, but so interesting, and even exciting. Not all varieties of primrose ...</string>
    <string name="title51">Growing the seedlings of Petunia</string>
    <string name="description51">Petunia is a herbaceous perennial plant from the nightshade family. The homeland is the hot tropics of Brazil, Bolivia, Argentina. But thanks to ...</string>
    <string name="title52">Gasiania</string>
    <string name="description52">South Africa is considered the homeland. Counted about 40 species. Perennial stunted or annual herbaceous plants. Gazania leaves ...</string>
    <string name="title53">Gaylardia</string>
    <string name="description53">About 25 species are counted, from Central, South and North America. Perennial, less often an annual. The stems of Gaylardia ...</string>
    <string name="title54">Gasteria</string>
    <string name="description54">Gasteria is a wonderful representative of the genus of the succulents of the Asphelov family. The birthplace of this flower is deserts, mountain slopes and anhydrous ...</string>
    <string name="title55">Carnation</string>
    <string name="description55">Carnation - Dianthus L. Family of Cloves - Caryophyllaceae Juss. One of the popular crops, so it is often planted ...</string>
    <string name="title56">Geichera</string>
    <string name="description56">Geichera is a famous long -term herbaceous plant. It belongs to the stonel family. The real homeland of this perennial is Western ...</string>
    <string name="title57">Heicherla</string>
    <string name="description57">The view of Heiheralla, turned out from the crossing of the Tiarelli core with Heyera. Heicheraella by the shape of the foliage and small size closer to ...</string>
    <string name="title58">Helenium</string>
    <string name="description58">The birthplace of Golenium is North America. More than 30 species of Gelenium are counted. Annual and perennial plants. Helenium has no long -term ...</string>
    <string name="title59">Dahlia</string>
    <string name="description59">Wintering of dahlias when dug up dahlia in the fall, according to various sources, the genus includes 25 species common in Colombia, Mexico ...</string>
    <string name="title60">Garden geranium</string>
    <string name="description60">Basically, large, with beautiful foliage and colorful flowers of plants in culture: a large -root or Balkan geranium in natural conditions ...</string>
    <string name="title61">Hyacinth</string>
    <string name="description61">Hyacinth is a perennial onion plant from the Mediterranean and Southeast Asia. Giacinta lovers are valued among flower growers ...</string>
    <string name="title62">Gymnocalicium</string>
    <string name="description62">Cacti began to gain great popularity. Miniature hedgehogs harmoniously fit into the interiors, protect from radiation of computers. But the most important thing ...</string>
    <string name="title63">Hypoestes</string>
    <string name="description63">Amazing beauty, the flower is a representative of the island of Madagascar and a nearby African areas. This is a very spectacular small, but ...</string>
    <string name="title64">Hippeastrum</string>
    <string name="description64">Onion indoor plant from the Amaralis family with large and unusually beautiful flowers and long leaves will not leave the hippeastrum ...</string>
    <string name="title65">Gypsophila</string>
    <string name="description65">The gypsophyla genus has more than 100 species growing in Africa, in Eurasia and Australia. Perennial, as well as annual ...</string>
    <string name="title66">Gladiolus</string>
    <string name="description66">This perennial tuber is a bulbous plant of the iris family is widespread in our country. In total, genus ...</string>
    <string name="title67">Gloxinia: landing and care ...</string>
    <string name="description67">One of the purpose of indoor plants is the decoration and addition of the interior. Gloxinia is one of the most beautiful representatives of home ...</string>
    <string name="title68">Gentian</string>
    <string name="description68">The genus has approximately 400 species of perennial and annual plants common in the tropical and moderate zone in all ...</string>
    <string name="title69">Goryanka</string>
    <string name="description69">To date, the genus has more than 50 types of burden. And this is not the limit, because annually nerds ...</string>
    <string name="title70">Avens</string>
    <string name="description70">More than 50 types of gravilate are known, growing in the cold and moderate zone of our planet. 7 ...</string>
    <string name="title71">Guzmania</string>
    <string name="description71">Guzmania is one of the most beautiful indoor flowers. It is popular thanks to delightful glossy leaves and multi -colored saturated ...</string>
    <string name="title72">Darlingtonium</string>
    <string name="description72">Darlingtonium is considered a rather predatory plant. Its leaves have a specific appearance and look like a hood that is ready ...</string>
    <string name="title73">Darmer</string>
    <string name="description73">Darmers clan contains only one species. Darmer is a thyroid homeland is North America, where it is found along the river banks in mountainous ...</string>
    <string name="title74">Decembrist: types and varieties ...</string>
    <string name="description74">The Decembrist is a room flowering plant. It begins to produce buds in late autumn, and in December flowers appear that create warm ...</string>
    <string name="title75">Decorative cabbage</string>
    <string name="description75">The genus has approximately 100 species of annual and biennial, sometimes perennial plants common in the moderate climate of Africa ...</string>
    <string name="title76">Delphinium</string>
    <string name="description76">They tell a beautiful legend about the dolphinium. The young man rejected by a capricious beauty turned into a dolphin and carried it out of the sea depth ...</string>
    <string name="title77">Jeffersonius</string>
    <string name="description77">Rod has only 2 types. One is found in North America, and the other is in the eastern ...</string>
    <string name="title78">Diasis</string>
    <string name="description78">Diasis is a heat -loving perennial and usually grown as an annual plant. Originally diagical from South America, where ...</string>
    <string name="title79">Design of the garden of flowers</string>
    <string name="description79">Traditionally, perennials are planted in borders or arbitrary groups. The border is a flower garden elongated along the axis of the correct rectangular shape ...</string>
    <string name="title80">Diploma</string>
    <string name="description80">It was first found in the central and southern regions of America. The Latin name is translated as “double glands” (nectaries). Despite...</string>
    <string name="title81">Diffenbachia</string>
    <string name="description81">One of the most beautiful indoor plants is diphenbachia. It is from South America, and its name is evergreen ...</string>
    <string name="title82">Dihondra landing and care ...</string>
    <string name="description82">Description of the Dihondra garden plant is a little remarkable plant, but growing next to other colors, shading them and creating an original ...</string>
    <string name="title83">Denter</string>
    <string name="description83">Rhizome perennial. The stems are straight, branched, fleshy, up to 100 cm high. The leaves are large, petiole, cirround, for the most part, basal, from above ...</string>
    <string name="title84">Doronikum</string>
    <string name="description84">The plant is Doronikum (in the native - “goat”, “yellow chamomile”, “spring chamomile”) - the herbaceous perennial plant of the complex of complexeral stages, its ...</string>
    <string name="title85">Flower delivery</string>
    <string name="description85">A bouquet of flowers presented from the heart will delight a loved one for a long time. Ordering a bouquet of flowers to give from a loved one is just ...</string>
    <string name="title86">Flower delivery in Moscow</string>
    <string name="description86">To date, a lot of flower salons deliver flowers in Moscow and companies offer to buy flowers. Except...</string>
    <string name="title87">Dracaena</string>
    <string name="description87">Amateur flower growers attribute the draca to false palm trees (recently such a term has appeared in flower shops). The basis for ...</string>
    <string name="title88">Dremlik</string>
    <string name="description88">Charming orchids, it turns out, can grow with us. Although they are not so bright and large, but such ...</string>
    <string name="title89">Living (Ayuga)</string>
    <string name="description89">Living or Ayuga - Ajuga Family: Gubo -color (lamiaceae). Homeland: Europe, Caucasus flowering: in June. Height: height 15-20 cm. Lighting of the tenacious in light shady ...</string>
    <string name="title90">Zamiokulkas</string>
    <string name="description90">This flower is very popular among most people, as it does not require much attention to its person ...</string>
    <string name="title91">Zamia</string>
    <string name="description91">Summy is an ancient native of the subtropics of America, which is the progenitor of modern fir trees, pines and other plants of this species ...</string>
    <string name="title92">Zephyrantes</string>
    <string name="description92">The description of Zephyrantes among the huge Amarillis family, including more than 2000 species, Zephyrantes occupies its special place. Delicate, pastel color ...</string>
    <string name="title93">Winter Garden</string>
    <string name="description93">In winter, a winter garden will become a corner of warmth and comfort in your house. The winter garden can be in your home the most ...</string>
    <string name="title94">Zolotarnik</string>
    <string name="description94">Solidago or goldener. The genus has approximately 120 species of the gold -ward, common in South and North America, in Europe ...</string>
    <string name="title95">Iberis</string>
    <string name="description95">Iberis is a perennial grassy bush, which belongs to the Cross -Bulge family. In the wild, the plant is found in mountain ...</string>
    <string name="title96">Ixor</string>
    <string name="description96">An evergreen shrub (lat. IXORA) is also called a "flame of forests." The plant is brought from the tropical forests of Asia. On the territory of India ...</string>
    <string name="title97">Ilang-Ylang</string>
    <string name="description97">This plant is considered exotic in our country, since its flowers have aromatic beautiful colors, of which ...</string>
    <string name="title98">Incarville</string>
    <string name="description98">The genus has 14 species common in China and Central Asia. Annual, biennial, as well as perennial herbaceous and ...</string>
    <string name="title99">Mortgage</string>
    <string name="description99">The clan of the Ipome, from the Binding family, is very wide, more than 500 species belong to it. Hypomey is common in the tropics of the New World ...</string>
    <string name="title100">Iridodictium</string>
    <string name="description100">Iridodictium is a bulbous plant that grows in the mountains of Transcaucasia, as well as in the mountainous areas of Central Asia. Small genus ...</string>
    <string name="no_such_index">\"There is no notes (%d) \"</string>
    <string name="linear_view">Linear view</string>
    <string name="two_columns">Cozy view</string>
</resources>